I want to say
말하고 싶어
To say I love you
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
Hey, what you doin’?
Waiting for the call back, uh
기다리잖아 Call back, uh
Vibe checked I’m bummed out
온도 Check 했잖아 나 꽁했어
Freezing I wanna be cuddled
추워 나 감기고 싶어
Hurry up, get me a blanket and tuck me in
Hurry up 이불 가져와 덮어줘
I wanna touch you
But you’re in the laptop
Come see me
날 보러 와
Like a coffee Take out
커피처럼 Take out
Ding diggy ding like a liggy ding ding
딩디기딩 Like a 리기딩딩
Wanna bing-bing spinning with you Errtime
너랑 같이 빙빙 놀고 싶어 Errtime
Butterflies in my stomach I’m sick
내 맘이 간질간질해 I’m sick
Always you and me like a symphony
We come together
Your rizz is flowing
너의 넘치는 매력
You make a bad day better yeah you
You make a good day better too
From the morning I wake up
눈을 뜨는 아침부터
Until the dawn when the moon sets
달이 지는 새벽까지
I’m happy thinking of you
네 생각에 행복해
You’ll never know
아마 모를걸
I want to say
말하고 싶어
To say I love you
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
And in this moonlight
We’re reaching new highs
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
L.O.V.E, L.O.V.E
Like scattered puzzle pieces
흐트러진 퍼즐같이
The words I’ve kept inside my mouth
입안에 담고 있는 말
Now, I want to say them out loud
이제는 말하고 싶어
Tonight, stop hesitating
Tonight 이제 그만 고민하고
Yeah boy, I’d like you to accept me so
Yeah boy, I’d like 날 거부하지 마 so
From the morning I wake up
눈을 뜨는 아침부터
Until the dawn when the moon sets
달이 지는 새벽까지
I’m happy thinking of you
네 생각에 행복해
You’ll never know
아마 모를걸
I want to say
말하고 싶어
To say I love you
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
And in this moonlight
We’re reaching new highs
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
Oh from the moment I first saw you
오 널 처음 본 순간부터
You keep appearing in my dreams
자꾸 내 꿈에 나와
And when I wake up, I long for more
눈 뜨면 아쉬워
No need to rush
I’ll come a little closer
좀 더 다가갈게 난 Little
I’m waiting on you too
Every day gets better
So glad that I found you
I want to say
말하고 싶어
To say I love you
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
And in this moonlight
We’re reaching new highs
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
Okay okay, I lost
Okay okay 내가 졌으니까
Tonight, I’ll accept your heart
오늘 너의 맘을 허락해
Okay okay, with the stars above
Okay okay 별이 떴으니까
I’ll close my eyes, holding your hands
손잡고 눈을 감을게
Okay okay, as we share our words
Okay okay 말을 섞으니까
Speech bubbles fill the air
말풍선이 가득해
But boy, I like you
Really really like you